ISMAEL **ESPINDOLA**

Full Stack Web Developer / Graphic Designer

in linkedin.com/in/espifreelancer

■ espifreelancer@gmail.com

+54 9 380 4646916



espifreelancer



@espifreelancer



espifreelancer.com



ABOUT ME

For more than two years, I have improved my skills as a Web Developer, both backend and frontend. I am truly determined to be an excellent developer. I also have more than 15 years as a Graphic Designer, experience that I integrate into each of my web design projects. I want to find my first formal IT job to provide all my motivation and desire to do new things.

WEB DEVELOPMENT SKILLS

RELEVANT COURSES

Python3	Oct. 2020	Node.js: Essential LinkedIn Learning, Full-stack web developer
Django	Nov. 2020 •	Node.js: Practical LinkedIn Learning, Full-stack web developer
Vue.js	Aug. 2020	JavaScript: Essential LinkedIn Learning, Full-stack web developer
PostgreSQL	Aug. 2020	JavaScript: Advanced - Regular Expressions LinkedIn Learning, Full-stack web developer
CSS/SASS	Aug. 2020	JavaScript: Advanced - Best Practices LinkedIn Learning, Full-stack web developer
AWS IBM/Watson	Oct. 2020	SQL: Essential LinkedIn Learning, Full-stack web developer
Linux	Oct. 2020	Learn relational database design LinkedIn Learning, Full-stack web developer
GIT	Jul. 2019	Amazon Web Services Practitioners Ministry of Planning and Industry
Testing	Oct. 2020	Web development: Automated quality control LinkedIn Learning, Full-stack web developer
GRAPHIC DESIGN SKILLS	Oct. 2019	Introduction to Software Testing National University of La Rioja (UNLAR)
Adobe XD	Nov. 2020 •	GitHub for developers LinkedIn Learning, Full-stack web developer
Figma	Aug. 2020	Learn SCRUM LinkedIn Learning, Full-stack web developer
CorelDRAW (Illustrator	Aug. 2020	Scrum: Roles LinkedIn Learning, Full-stack web developer
Photoshop	Nov. 2020	Teamwork LinkedIn Learning
		•

Blender



ISMAEL **ESPINDOLA**

Full Stack Web Developer Graphic Designer



espifreelancer@gmail.com

(+54 9 380 4646916

LANGUAGES

English Basic. Technical reading.

Spanish Native

EVENTS & WORKSHOPS

Maratona Behind the Code 2020 IBM Latin America

- Watson Assistant
- Watson Knowkedge Studio
- Watson NLU
- Watson Machine Learning
- O Jupyter Notebooks
- Feature engineering

PERSONAL QUALITIES

Transparent

Empathic

Autodidact

NON-CERTIFIED COURSES

Jul. 2017 • Python pildorasinformaticas, POO

Dec. 2017 Diango

mozilla.org / developers

Oct. 2019 • Django REST codigofacilito

Aug. 2019 PostgreSQL
Tecnología Binaria

Aug. 2018 JavaScript desde 0 pildorasinformaticas

Jan. 2020 • Vue.js 2
Bluuweb

Feb. 2019 • Git makigas

Feb. 2019 • Ul Design Course Francisco Aguilera G.

EXPERIENCES

2014 - 2019 🔘

CHIMICHANGA Graphic designer

- · Adaptation of images to transfer on clothing.
- · Photo retouching.
- · Logo creation, event packaging, brochures, etc
- Preparation of jobs for printing on different media.
- Color separation for screen printing, image preparation for cutting plotter.
- Traditional and digital illustration.

2003 - 2016

TELESTAR

Graphic designer, printer and computer equipment maintenance. Customer attention.

- Technical maintenance equipment, networks, printers and photocopiers.
- Preparing documents for printing.
- Creation of posters, brochures, photo retouching, video editing.

2003 - 2003

RADIO UNIVERSIDAD UNLAR Radiophonic technical operator

- · Radio broadcast programming.
- · Active participation in production teams.
- Performance as an assistant sound engineer.

EDUCATION

2000 - 2004 O Industrial engineering

Three years, unfinished career